[IMA] This house is huge, dear!
You fit right in!
- We hit the jackpot!
- [LAUGHS]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh my god, guard!
I told you not to let
street urchins in!
- Street urchins?
You know what, here you go.
You may leave now.
Hey!
We're not beggars!
My father is the cousin
of the cousin
of the uncle of the cousin
of the nephew of the cousin
of the cousin's cousin
of Don Nato!
My daughter is so excellent.
[SMOOCHES]
- You better tell her!
- [SIGHS]
Guard!
[SHERYN] Guard!
Oh! I'm the guard.
Let them in.
They're at the right place.
This is Miss June Sampaga
and her mom.
But, Attorney, who's this
diva wannabe anyway?
How are you a wannabe
and stingy?
Is this face worth only
five pesos to you? Hmph!
This is Miss Sheryn Cruz.
The assistant of Don Nato.
You'll be seeing her
most of the time
because Don Nato's office
is actually situated here.
[WHISPERS] An assistant...
Please bring this
inside our house.
Please?
Excuse me, it isn't yours yet.
Don't get carried away.
And I'm sure...
Ping won't like you anyway.
You're sure?
- [IMA MUTTERING]
- [JUNE] Uh...
Attorney, is Ping my...
husband-to-be?
[ZIA] Yes.
Your future husband.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Eh?
- Dear, why is he like that?
Ma, you two
suit each other better!
[WHISPERING] Hey,
watch your words!
Uh, do we really need
to sleep beside each other?
[ZIA] Oh, naturally!
He's your husband!
[GULPS]
[JUNE] He has one foot
in the grave already!
You do it!
[IMA] No way!
Attorney, what is all this?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS]
Uh...
I'll just imagine
that our vinegar business
will boom if I do this!
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[IN UNISON] It's you?!